Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy

_Last updated August 5th, 2021._

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at WxSocial (“**Company**”, “**we**”, “**us**”, or “**our**”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at info@wxsocial.us.

When you visit our website, [wxsocial.app](https://wxsocial.app/) (the “**Website**“), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy notice that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Services immediately.

This privacy notice applies to all information collected through our website, as well as any related services, sales, marketing or events.

**Please read this privacy notice carefully as it will help you understand what we do with the information that we collect.**

### What Information Do We Collect?

**Personal Information Provided By You**

We collect personal information, including display names and usernames, email addresses, passwords, and other similar information disclosed by you when you create an account on our website.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We also collect some non-identifying information when you visit our website, which may include your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, referring URLs, device name, country, location, and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many websites, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.  The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic usage and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type and settings and information about your activity in the Services (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called ‘crash dumps’) and hardware settings).

* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet or other device you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, and operating system configuration information.

* _Location Data._ We collect information data such as information about your device’s imprecise location. We may use technologies to collect geolocation data that tells us your current location (based on your IP address). You can opt out of allowing us to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Locations settings on your device.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We use personal information collected via our Services for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.

We use the information we collect or receive:

* **To facilitate account creation and logon processes.** If you choose to link your account with us to a third-party account (such as your Twitter account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process for the performance of the contract.

* **Request feedback.** We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.
* **To enable user-to-user communications.** We may use your information in order to enable user-to-user communications with each user’s consent.
* **To manage user accounts**. We may use your information for the purposes of managing our account and keeping it in working order.

* **To send administrative information to you.** We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.
* **To protect our Services.** We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Services safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).
* **To enforce our terms, conditions and policies for business purposes, to comply with legal and regulatory requirements or in connection with our contract.**
* **To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.** If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

* **For other business purposes.** We may use your information for other business purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing and your experience. We may use and store this information in aggregated and anonymized form so that it is not associated with individual end users and does not include personal information. We will not use identifiable personal information without your consent.

### Will Your Information Be Shared With Anyone?

We may process or share your data that we hold based on the following legal basis:

* **Consent:** We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information in a specific purpose.
* **Legitimate Interests:** We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.
* **Performance of a Contract:** Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.
* **Legal Obligations:** We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).
* **Vital Interests:** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

Do We Use Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies?
--------------------------------------------------

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information.

### How Long Do We Keep Your Information?

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

### How Do We Keep Your Information Safe?

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security, and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

What Are Your Privacy Rights?
-----------------------------

If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

If you are resident in Switzerland, the contact details for the data protection authorities are available here: [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html).

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at info@wxsocial.us.

**Account Information**

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can log in to your account settings and update your user account.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

### Do California Residents Have Specific Privacy Rights?

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with a Service, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g. backups, etc.).  

**CCPA Privacy Notice**

The California Code of Regulations defines a “resident” as:

(1) every individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose and

(2) every individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purposeAll other individuals are defined as “non-residents.”  
If this definition of “resident” applies to you, certain rights and obligations apply regarding your personal information.  
**What categories of personal information do we collect?**  
We have collected the following categories of personal information in the past twelve (12) months:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| Identifiers | Contact details, such as real name, alias, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, and account name | YES |
| Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute | Name and contact information | YES |
| Geolocation data | Device location (from IP address) | YES |

We may also collect other personal information outside of these categories in instances where you interact with us in-person, online, or by phone or mail in the context of:

* Receiving help through our customer support channels
* Participation in customer surveys or contests; and
* Facilitation in the delivery of our Services and to respond to your inquiries

**How do we use and share your personal information?**

More information about our data collection and sharing practices can be found in this privacy notice.

You may contact us by email at info@wxsocial.us.

If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your right to opt-out, we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

**Will your information be shared with anyone else?**  
WxSocial has not disclosed or sold any personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months. WxSocial will not sell personal information in the future belonging to website visitors, users and other consumers.

**Your rights with respect to your personal data**

**Right to request deletion of the data – Request to delete**  
You can ask for the deletion of your personal information. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities.

**Right to be informed – Request to know**  
Depending on the circumstances, you have a right to know:

* whether we collect and use your personal information;
* the categories of personal information that we collect;
* the purposes for which the collected personal information is used;
* whether we sell your personal information to third parties;
* the categories of personal information that we sold or disclosed for a business purpose;
* the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and
* the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information.

In accordance with applicable law, we are not obligated to provide or delete consumer information that is de-identified in response to a consumer request or to re-identify individual data to verify a consumer request.

**Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights**  
We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

**Verification process**  
Upon receiving your request, we will need to verify your identity to determine you are the same person about whom we have the information in our system. These verification efforts require us to ask you to provide information so that we can match it with the information you have previously provided us. For instance, depending on the type of request you submit, we may ask you to provide certain information so that we can match the information you provide with the information we already have on file, or we may contact you through a communication method (e.g. phone or email) that you have previously provided to us. We may also use other verification methods as the circumstances dictate.  
We will only use personal information provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. To the extent possible, we will avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. If, however, if we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity, and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete such additionally provided information as soon as we finish verifying you.

**Other privacy rights**

* you may object to the processing of your personal data
* you may request correction of your personal data if it is incorrect or no longer relevant, or ask to restrict the processing of the data
* you can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf in accordance with the CCPA.
* you may request to opt-out from future selling of your personal information to third parties. Upon receiving a request to opt-out, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than 15 days from the date of the request submission.

To exercise these rights, you can contact us by email at info@wxsocial.us. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.

### Do We Make Updates To This Notice?

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

How Can You Contact Us About This Notice?
-----------------------------------------

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at info@wxsocial.us.

[](javascript:void(0);)
